<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Workflows, | CSS &amp; Projects]]></title>
  <link href="http://Marekje.github.io/blog/categories/workflows/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://Marekje.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-08-16T12:56:59+02:00</updated>
  <id>http://Marekje.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Marekje]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scrum Workflows : Development and Testing]]></title>
    <link href="http://Marekje.github.io/blog/2014/07/24/scrum-workflows-development-and-testing/"/>
    <updated>2014-07-24T08:47:37+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://Marekje.github.io/blog/2014/07/24/scrum-workflows-development-and-testing</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>At work, we use <em>Scrum</em>. An agile methodologie where you make one-week increments to your project. Each increment is build with enough <em>user-stories</em> to fill a week of development (look for <a href="">velocity</a> in this very blog).</p>

<p>Developers are obviously important in this process, as they build the project. While important, you could reduce their project management part to two workflows.</p>

<p>The main one is the <strong>Development workflow</strong> :</p>

<h3>Development workflow :</h3>

<p>The developer looks for the next Card he has to do in the Sprint Backlog. He puts the card in <code>Implementation</code>, and work on it.
Once finished, he pushes the card in <code>Implementation done</code> (A tester is going to take it, but it does not really matter for the developer).</p>

<p>The second worflow is not meant only for developers, but rather for everyone on board :</p>

<h3><em>“I got an idea”</em> workflow</h3>

<p>When someone has an idea, he writes it down in the <em>Product Backlog</em>. If possible, he should write it as a user-story, telling the story of someone achieving an action using the project.</p>

<blockquote><p>As a user, I want to rank lists according to their importance because it will help me prioritize them for the next iteration.
<em>A user-story, from the viewpoint of a user</em></p></blockquote>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
